## **BEZA MEKONNEN GADISSA**

Address: Addis Ababa, Ethiopia Phone Number: +251932264643

Email Address: bezamekonnen35@gmail.com

Links: LinkedIn | Github

#### **Profile**

An IT professional with one year of experience as a Technical Specialist Support and React Developer, skilled in cloud computing and web development. I am excited to bring forward the skills I have grasped. Always open to new opportunities to expand my scope of knowledge.

## **Work Experience**

## January 2024

Technical specialist support and React Developer

I worked as a Technical Specialist at HahuCloud Technologies, I was responsible for maintaining the technical aspects of the server and assisting customers with their technical inquiries. I undertook React projects, further expanding my development skills.

## **July 2020-August 2020**

Front-End developer at Purpose Black

This internship demonstrated my skills in front-end development, including React, JavaScript, and HTML/CSS. I was able to work effectively as part of a team and to meet deadlines

### **June 2022 – August 2022**

System testing at Ethio Telecom

In this internship, I participated in the system testing team which handled planning, execution, defect reporting, and, bug fixing. This experience lead me to see other aspects of the technical part and helped me grow in a new work environment and overcome challenges.

### **April 2023**

Front-end developer at a Game Jam event

I participated in a game jam event as a front-end developer in which I participated as a fresh beginner to the gaming world. I participated in Designing the user interface (UI) for the game, Coding the UI in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and Working with the game's developers to ensure that the UI is functional and meets the game's requirements to help the project stand out.

#### **Skills**

#### **Technical skills**

- Html/CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Database
- Operating system
- Data Entry
- MS office

## **Interpersonal and Communication skills**

- Proficient in spoken and written English communication
- Active listening and problem-solving
- Organized and professional
- Fast learner and adaptive to any kind of environment

## **Education**

# Bachelor's degree in computer science and engineering Adama Science and Technology University

September 2018-July 2023

• GPA- 3.0

# Training and certificate

- HTML certificate from Frontend mentor
- CSS certificate from Frontend mentor
- JavaScript certificate From frontend mentor
- Data Analysis certificate From Udacity